



saba Katsadze

Date of birth: 12/12/1999 | **Nationality:** Georgian | **Phone number:**

(+44) 07519297404 (Mobile) | Email address: katsadzesaba2@gmail.com

Website: https://ss19991212.github.io/Saba CV.github.io/ Facebook:

https://www.facebook.com/saba.kacadze.7

WhatsApp Messenger: 07519297404

Address: Glasgow, G72 8UR, Glasgow, United Kingdom (Home)

ABOUT ME

I am a young professional from Georgia. I have bachelor's degree in International Relations and am currently studying on an Erasmus Mundus Joint Master's degree program called Central and East European, Russian and Eurasian studies. My professional experience is the following: I have undergone an internship at US embassy in Tbilisi in public affairs section, an internship at the National Center for Education Quality Enhancement of Georgia and an internship at the Administration of the President of Georgia at the communications department. It was during the last internship that I was accepted on the EMJMD program. However, due to falling ill, I had to abruptly end the internship and defer the studies on the MA course by a year. But I managed to survive and emerge victorious over brain cancer and have returned to my studies. Recently I have started expanding my skillset for employability purposes and have become interested in the promising field of Digital Marketing. I have obtained the certificate from Google's Digital Garage, Digital Marketing course, alongside Coursera's Specialization in SEO course. As well as Codeacademy's certificate of HTML/CSS to complement my SEO skills. Currently I am studying Google Analytics and plan to improve my data analysis skills by studying SQL for market research.

WORK EXPERIENCE

30/06/2020 - 22/01/2021 Tbilisi, Georgia

INTERN OF THE PUBLIC AFFAIRS SECION UNITED STATES EMBASSY IN GEORGIA

Member of the Press Team. Mainly tasked with preparing daily news reports, translating and preparing transcripts.

01/09/2021 - 10/01/2022 Georgia

INTERN OF THE PLANNING, RESEARCH AND INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS DEPARTMENT LEPL NATIONAL CENTER FOR EDUCATION QUALITY ENHANCEMENT

Mainly tasked with double-checking, reviewing and translating documents, as well as assisting other members of the team in executing day-to-day tasks.

22/12/2021 - 03/2022 Tbilisi, Georgia

INTERN OF THE COMMUNICATIONS OFFICE ADMINISTRATION OF THE PRESIDENT OF GEORGIA

Monitoring political trends domestically and abroad. Working on President's visibility through website and social media management. Preparing daily news reports and assisting the staff in administrative duties.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

08/09/2023 - CURRENT Glasgow, United Kingdom

INTERNATIONAL MASTER'S IN CENTRAL AND EAST EUROPEAN, RUSSIAN AND EURASIAN STUDIES Tartu, Glasgow & Jagiellonian Universities

STUDENT Caucasus University

Address 1 Paata Saakadze Street | Website https://cu.edu.ge/

DELEGATE AT EUROPEAN SCHOOL OF POLICY AND REFORMS Konrad Adenauer Stiftung

Website https://www.kas.de/de/home

DELEGATE AT GLOBAL CHALLENGES FORUM 2019 Future Diplomats' Club

Website https://www.facebook.com/FutureDiplomatsClub/

CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION IN THE YEARLY STUDENT CONFERENCE - 2021 Caucasus University

Website https://cu.edu.ge/

CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION IN THE ESSAY COMPETITION OF "NATO, GEORGIA AND CURRENT SECURITY CHALLENGES: THE 2018 BRUSSELS SUMMIT AND BEYOND" Embassy of Bulgaria

Website https://www.mfa.bg/en/embassies/georgia

United Kingdom

CERTIFICATE OF SEO Coursera

Website Coursera.org

United Kingdom

CERTIFICATE OF GOOGLE'S DIGITAL MARKETING COURSE Google

Website Google.com

United Kingdom

HTML & CSS CERTIFICATE CodeAcademy

Website Codeacademy.com

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **GEORGIAN**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C1	C1	C1
RUSSIAN	B1	B1	B1	B1	B1
FRENCH	A2	A2	A2	A2	A2
SPANISH	A2	A2	A2	A2	A2
POLISH	A1	A1	A1	A1	A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Basic Digital Marketing \mid Basic Knowledge of SEO \mid Copywriting (basic) \mid HTMl & CSS \mid Google (Google Ads, Google Analytics) \mid Microsoft Excel